#### Paulo Leonardo Benatto

London, UK benatto@gmail.com Phone: 07405110040 Post Code: SW16 2BU

Summary

Bachelor in computer science having expertise in software development, good professional relationship and focused at work. With 6 years of professional experience in software development using basically, C/C++, I am now looking for new challenges and opportunities that allow me to learn new technologies and work with new people. I have interest in software development (C/C++, Python, Java, Lua, ShellScript and Go) and Linux Operating System administration.

Education

Universidade Estadual do Oeste do Parana, BSc in Computer Science, December 2007.

Experience

DBA

Dec 2013 - Feb 2014

 $System\ Analyst$ 

Main Technologies: Linux, Python, Raspberry PI and C;

Member of a team responsible to design and develop a system to analyze vehicle traffic on Brazilian highways. Basically my task was read files with a lot of records and parse all information, store in memory and report this information in a human readable. In parallel I attended of a project to develop a parking meter system, using python language and Raspberry PI. My main task was do inter-process communication using DBus.

SEC+ Dec 2012 - Dec 2013

 $System\ Analyst$ 

Main Technologies: Linux, Python, Django Framework, JavaScript and C;

Back-end development of web system for intelligent monitoring and management of natural disasters using Python and the Django framework. Front-end with Javascript (JQuery, Bootstrap, Google Maps API), JSON, HTML5, CSS. Modeling and use of object-relational database and geographic objects with PostgreSQL/PostGIS.

### Digitro Technology - NDS

Jan 2012 - Dec 2012

 $System\ analyst$ 

Main Technologies: Linux, C/C++, Java, ShellScript;

Member of the team responsible to design and develop the roadmap features of a product called Guardião used to intercept calls and internet trafic of people whose are being investigated by the police. Specifically allocated on the design and development of a module which main goal is to intercept the actions done on Facebook, WhatsApp and Hotmail of a target, using the gathered data to cross reference with another possible targets.

# Digitro Technology - STE

Set 2008 - Dec 2011

System analyst

Main Technologies: Linux, VoIP, C/C++, shellscript, protocols: UDP, TCP, SIP;

VoIP systems development basically using C/C++ languages and libraries such as GLib and Sofia-SIP. Working in a team I attended big projects, like: **Softphone**, software program for making telephone calls over the Internet using a general purpose computer, rather than using dedicated hardware, and an **IP Phone**.

Linux administration, python, lua, shell scripting, network protocol analysis are common activities in large projects.

Skills Base

 $Operating\ System:$  Linux (Debian, Ubuntu, CentOS), Windows NT/XP/Vista/7 and OSX;

Networkings: TCP/IP protocol suite;

Progamming Languages: C/C++, Pascal, Python, JavaScript, plus some experience with Lua and Java;

Virtualization: VirtualBox, VMWare, plus some experience with Xen;

Languages: Fluent in Portuguese, Intermediate in English and Spanish;

## Open Source Projects

- libpenetra: The libpenetra was created with the goal of studying the windows binary format known as Portable Executable (PE). With libpenetra you can access all information about PE binaries. (https://github.com/patito/libpenetra)
- libmalelf: The libmalelf is an evil library that SHOULD be used for good! It was developed with the intent to assist in the process of infecting binaries and provide a safe way to analyze malwares. (https://github.com/SecPlus/libmalelf)
- malelf: Malelf is a tool that uses librallelf to dissect and infect ELF binaries. (https://github.com/SecPlus/malelf)

### More Info

- $\bullet$  Linkedin: http://www.linkedin.com/in/benatto
- **Github**: https://github.com/patito